U.S. Manpower Administration "Manpower Daily Reporter" Newsletters 5380
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Manpower Administration "Manpower Daily Reporter" Newsletters
1966-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Manpower Administration
5380
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Monthly issues of "Manpower Daily Reporter" for 1966-1970
5620259
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 15, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
United States.; United States. Department of Labor.Manpower Administration.
5620259
- June, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday June 10, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday June 8, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday June 7, 1966. Item is in English.
- July, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 29, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 28, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 27, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 26, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 25, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 22, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 21, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 20, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 19, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 18, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 15, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday July 14, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 13, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 12, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday July 11, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 8, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday July 6, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday July 5, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday July 1, 1966. Item is in English.
- August, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 31, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 30, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 29, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 22, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 19, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 18, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 9, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 8, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday August 5, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday August 4, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday August 3, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday August 2, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday August 1, 1966. Item is in English.
- September, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 30, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 29, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 28, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 27, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 26, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 23, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 22, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 21, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 20, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 19, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 16, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 15, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 14, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 13, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday September 12, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 9, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 8, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday September 7, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday September 6, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday September 2, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday September 1, 1966. Item is in English.
- October, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 28, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 27, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 26, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Copy 2. Wednesday October 26, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 25, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 24, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 21, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 20, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 19, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 18, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 17, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 14, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 13, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 12, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 11, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 10, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday October 7, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday October 6, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday October 5, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday October 4, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday October 3, 1966. Item is in English.
- November, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 30, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 29, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 28, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 25, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 23, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 22, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 21, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 18, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 17, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 16, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 15, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 14, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 10, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 9, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 8, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 7, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 4, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 3, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 2, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 1, 1966. Item is in English.
- December, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 22, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 21, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 20, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 19, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 16, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 15, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 14, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 13, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 12, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 9, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 8, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 7, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 6, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 5, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 2, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 1, 1966. Item is in English.
- January, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 31, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 30, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 27, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 25, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 24, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 23, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 20, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 19, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 18, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 17, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 16, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 13, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 12, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 11, 1967. Item is in English.